Sincro: wyxchari
【翻译】巴蛮子sz
【时间轴】巴蛮子sz
【校对】巴蛮子sz
基于 opentitles.org 英文字幕翻译
我是-你的-仆人. 我是-你的-仆人...
I am your servant. I am your servant...
Lesterson, 它们居然可以说话!
So Lesterson, they're even capable of speech!
是的. 为什么不呢? 毕竟, 他们有一定的智力.
Yes. But then, why not? After all, they have a certain intelligence.
是的我知道, 但是...
Yes I know, but...
但是, 是不是... 我们可以控制住.
But is... is it... it is... an intelligence that we can control.
你想的无非就是获准可以继续你的实验?
So what you want is permission to continue your experiments?
总督, 想想这意味着什么, 我们可以让他们去挖矿. 我们的生产力可以翻番了!
Governor, think what it would mean if we were to set it to work
in the mines. It could double our production overnight!
想想这可能给我们整体经济带来什么效果.
Consider the effects it could have on our whole economy.
是的, 还可以地球地球带来... 是的, 是的, 他们会很感激的.
Yes, and the effect of that on Earth...
Yes. Yes, they could be very grateful.
我该阻止你. 我会的!
I shall stop you. I will!
好了 Lesterson, 授权你可以继续.
All right Lesterson, permission granted.
授权? 授什么权?
Permission? Permission for what?
继续我的工作啊, 监察员.
To continue my work, Examiner.
但是... 但是你没听见我说什么了吗? Daleks必须全部毁掉!
But... But didn't you all hear what I said?
The Daleks must be destroyed!
吼, 吼. 绝不!
Ho, ho. Never!
很好. 如果我的命令不好使 - 那地球的命令总可以了! 过来 Ben, Polly.
Very well. If not by my order - then by Earth's! Come Ben, Polly.
啊, 监察员. 等一下. 告诉我, 你为什么如此针对这个项目?
Ah, Examiner. Just a moment.
Tell me, why are you so against this project?
我告诉过你! 我意识到我无法给你任何证据, 但你们大难临头还一无所知!
But I've told you! I realise I can't give you any proof,
but you've no idea of the danger!
不会.
No.
是的, 大难! 只要通讯一恢复我就要联系地球.
Yes. Danger! I shall be contacting Earth just as soon as
radio communications have been restored.
你是我的仆人, 是吗?
You're my servant, are you?
我... 是.
I... I am.
很好. 关掉你自己. 快. 我命令! 马上!
Very well. Immobilise yourself. Go on. I order it! Immediately!
哈!
Huh!
Lesterson.
你为什么不遵守? 你已经收到命令了.
Why did you stop obeying? You were given an order.
他-已经-走了.
He has gone.
你只遵守...
Then you obey only...
他的-命令-是-错误的. 我-要是-关掉-自己-就-不能-服务于-人了.FIXME
His order was wrong. I cannot serve human beings if I am immobilised.
你-给了-我-能量. 你的-命令-是-对的. 我-服务于-你.
You gave me power. Your orders are right. I serve you.
Lesterson. Lesterson, 他会分析. 你不是说它智力有限吗?
Lesterson. Lesterson, it reasons.
Just how limited is its intelligence?
喔, 没理由担心这个, 总督. 你等着瞧它能做多少事情!
Now, there is no cause for... for concern, Governor.
Just you wait until you see the amount of work it can do!
现在, 我要让你经历你自己的生活了. 跟我来, Dalek.
And now, I'm really going to put you through your paces.
Follow me, Dalek.
我-服从.
I obey.
居然这样!
That's it!
我们应该跟 Quinn 呆在一起.
We should have stayed with Quinn.
我们本来也帮不了他的, Polly, 即使我们想帮. 总督已经做出决定了.
Well, we couldn't have helped him Polly, even if we'd wanted to.
The Governor's already reached his verdict.
Polly: 但他没有谋杀真正的监察员. 我确定他没有.
But he didn't murder the real Examiner. I'm sure he didn't.
(博士: 电缆. 剪刀. 磁带.)
Wire. Scissors. Tape.
哦, 这样. 我看这帮人忙于内部吵来吵去, 做不了什么事情都做不成.
Oh, well. The way I see it this lot's too busy arguing
amongst themselves to do much about anything.
不管怎样, 排排重点. Daleks 是最重要的事!
Anyway, first things first. The Daleks are the important thing!
啊! 恭喜你, Ben!
Ah! Congratulations, Ben!
我做什么了? 我做什么了?
What'd I do? What'd I do?
你用了你的脑子, 你干了这个. Daleks 是最重要的事情!
You just used your brains, that's what you did.
The Daleks are the most important thing!
我仍然认为 Quinn 是无辜的.
I still think Quinn's innocent.
我怎么能与叛乱分子结成同盟呢?
How can I be in league with the rebels?
证据已经证实了.
The evidence confirms it.
是我提醒他们注意危险的.
It was I that warned of their dangers.
这是你总体计划的一部分!
As part of your overall plan!
你甚至都没有认真对待.
You wouldn't even take the matter seriously.
我那时错了, 现在我有机会来纠正它了!
If I was wrong then, I have a chance to rectify it now!
如果你是这个态度, 我建议我们...
If that's going to be your attitude, I suggest that we...
Quinn! 我们一件一件捋清楚. 首先, 监察员被攻击了, 这是毫无疑问的.
Quinn! Let us conduct this inquiry in an orderly manner.
Now, the Examiner was attacked, there can be no question of that.
被监察员抓到手的纽扣也是你衣服上不见的那个.
And the button grabbed by the Examiner was missing from your suit.
是的, 如果你还有什么补充, 你最好现在就说.
Yes, if you've got anything to add to that, you'd better say it now.
我没有袭击他. 我没有理由. 他是我请求派来的!
I didn't attack the man. I had no reason to.
I was the one that sent for him!
你请求的?!
You sent for him?!
在现在这情况下, 必须这样做。我也不可能破坏电波通讯.
It was necessary. Under the circumstances,
I'd hardly be likely to sabotage the radio communications.
不过... 为什么 Quinn? 为什么?
But... but why Quinn? Why?
因为那些叛乱分子!
Because of the rebels!
叛乱分子! 只不过有一两个狂热分子.
The rebels! They're nothing more than one or two fanatics.
你我都知道他们...
You know as well as I do that they...
除非你是想制造些事端 - 想挖总督的墙脚吧.
Unless you're trying to create trouble here
- to undermine the Governor's position.
Bragen, 你最好解释一下.
Bragen, you'd better explain that.
如果你被除掉了, 谁顶你的位子? 当然是副总督. 这就是所有问题的真正原因, 对吧 Quinn?
If you're removed, who takes your place? The Deputy Governor, of course.
And that's the real reason behind all this trouble, isn't it Quinn?
继续.
Go on.
你在水银沼泽袭击了监察员, 嫁祸于叛乱分子. 然后又破坏了电台 - 也归咎于叛乱分子.
You attack the Examiner in the mercury swamp and blame it on the rebels.
Then you sabotage the radio - blame that on the rebels too.
把他带走!
Get him out of my sight!
Hensell, 在你听取这些荒谬的指控之前...
Hensell, before you listen to these preposterous allegations...
Quinn 是我自己选的. 我培养他干这个工作. 为什么啊, 要不了几年时间, 他就能坐在这个位子上了啊!
I chose Quinn myself. I trained him for the job.
Why, in a few years time, he'd have had this seat!
总督, 有时候, 几年时间也嫌太长, 等不了啊.
Sometimes Governor, a few years is a long time to wait.
哦, Bragen?
Oh, Bragen?
总督?
Governor?
你接替 Quinn 的工作. 目前来说, 你是副总督.
You will assume Quinn's duties. As of now, you are Deputy Governor.
啊!
Ah!
我希望你知道自己在做什么!
I hope you know what you're doing!
我也是!
So do I!
非常好. 非常好.
Excellent. excellent.
我还以为我们在追查的是 Daleks, 而不是你在玩弄的这个控制盒!
But I thought we were after the Daleks,
not this control unit you've nicked!
要是我们能找到一个... 啊, 对了!
If only we could find a... Ah, yes!
他对这事不怎么上心, 是不?
He's a right little delinquent, isn't he?
博士, 你到底在干什么?
Doctor, what on Earth are you up to?
哦!
Ooh!
啊! 我们真有点进展了!
Ah! Now we're really getting somewhere!
看着, 博士, 我并不想看起来比较负能量, 但这跟 Daleks 有什么关系?
Look Doctor, I don't want to appear dim,
but how's this going to do the Daleks in?
他们认为是 Lesterson 有主导权, 但我觉得不是. Daleks 在利用他.
They think that Lesterson's the driving force,
but I don't. The Daleks are using him.
那怎么办?
But how?
有个问题. 砸碎 Daleks 的话, 这里的人会把我们锁起来或者干脆干掉我们 FIXME
Problem. Smash the Daleks, and the people here will lock us up or kill us.
任由 Daleks 乱来的话, 我们会被 exterminated（终结）.
Let the Daleks go, and we'll all be exterminated.
我们可以回 TARDIS 去. 至少在那里是安全的.
We could just go back to the TARDIS.
At least we'd be safe to think there.
哦, 是的, that's coming on.
Oh yes, that's coming on.
哦, 你会跟他说的, 是吗?
Oh, you talk to him, will you?
博士, 如果你告诉我们你要干什么的话, 也许我们能帮上忙.
Doctor look, if you told us what you were up to,
perhaps we could help you.
千万不能低估他们中的任何一个. Lesterson 是个一流的科学家, 一流的FIXME
Mustn't underestimate any of them.
Lesterson's a first class scientist, first class.
他打开了舱体, 还发现 Daleks 可以被重新激活.
He opened the capsule. He realised that the Daleks could be reactivated.
是, 那可能就是答案. 我们不如把 Lesterson 绑架了吧, 把他藏起来一阵子 FIXME
Yeah, that could be the answer. Let's kidnap Lesterson,
and hide him away for a bit.
这样就可以阻止他救活那些 Daleks, 对吧?
Well, it would stop him bringing the Daleks back to life, wouldn't it?
我觉得这个主意真不错.
I thought it was pretty bright.
这下可以了.
There we are.
什么?
What is it?
这是什么东西? 可能是我们所有问题的答案.
What is it? It could be the answer to all our problems.
监察员, 别让他们用叛乱的事情把你糊弄了. 他们势力强大.
Ah Examiner, don't let them fool you about the rebels.
They're strong.
找出他们在哪里开会.
Try and find out where they hold their meetings.
放开他!
Leave him alone!
没事的, Polly.
It's all right, Polly.
我们会帮助他, Polly. 不过得晚点.
We'll help him Polly, but later.
虽然说...
Yes but...
现在这个场景下, 一点点的不公是好过所有人都遭殃的 FIXME
Now, this is a case where a little injustice
is better than wholesale slaughter.
我们想要的东西在 Lesterson 的实验室里. 来吧.
What we want is in Lesterson's laboratory. Come along.
难以置信! 好, 下面我们进行第14项测试.
Incredible! Well, let's move on to test fourteen.
我-准备-好了.
I am ready.
把钠与酒精掺在一起, 会产生什么后果?
When sodium acts on ethyl alcohol,
what is the resulting derivative?
乙醇-钠. C2-H5-ONa.
Sodium ethoxide. C2 H5 ONA.
只需要5秒, Janley! 而且这点时间都用来念答案了.
Just five seconds, Janley! Just the time it took to speak the answer.
又答对了.
Right too.
当然是对的! 你能想象这个机器人用的是哪种正子脑吗, Janley?
But of course it's right! Look, can you imagine
what kind of positronic brain this robot has, Janley?
想想他得存有多少知识. 硫酸.
Think of the store of knowledge that it must carry. Sulphuric acid.
H2 SO4.
啊, 你看?
Ah, you see?
我可以进来吗?
May I come in?
你想干什么?
What do you want?
哦, 只是来看看你这里进展如何.
Oh, ah, just to see how you're getting on.
如果你想要...
If you think...
不, 别这样! 我... 不是来找麻烦的. ... 我只是很有兴趣, 仅此而已.
No, please! I'm... I'm not here to cause trouble.
I... I'm just interested, that's all.
自你达到 Vulcan 以来, 除了干扰和干涉之外什么也没做过.
You've done nothing but meddle and interfere ever
since you landed on Vulcan.
这个... 是我给了权限打开舱体, 是吧? 现在请继续.
Well, I... I did give you permission to open up the capsule,
now didn't I? Please, carry on.
你不打算阻止我?
And you won't try to stop me?
阻止你? 不, 当然不. 咱们俩一开始就不怎么对付, Lesterson,
Stop you? No, of course not. We get off on the wrong foot, Lesterson
不过... 我是一个讲理的人... 我在想, 也许是我太鲁莽了.
but... but I'm a reasonable man and...
and I've been thinking, perhaps I was hasty.
好吧, 如果... 如果你真想要休战.
Well, if you... if you... if you really want to call a truce.
休战? 亲爱的家伙, ... 我期望可以成为朋友!
A truce? My dear fellow, I... I'd like to be friends!
好. 好. 很好, 你可以呆着.
Yes. Yes. Very well, you may stay.
哦, 谢谢你. 谢谢你. 也许你想自己娱乐一小会儿
Oh, thank you. Thank you. Perhaps you'd like to
amuse yourselves for a little while.
这里是实验室. 是.
Laboratory. Yes.
好的, 我可以过来. 好.
All right, I can come now. Right.
我得出去几分钟, Lesterson, 可以吧?
I just have to slip out for a few minutes, Lesterson, alright?
啊, 可以, 可以. 唔, 那么, 监察员, 我们开始测试一下他的物理知识?
Ah, yes, yes. Um, very well then.
Examiner, shall we test its knowledge of physics?
哦, 太好了, 啊, 请开始吧.
Oh, oh, splendid, splendid. Ah, huh, please, please, carry on.
谢谢你... 热力学第一定律是什么?
Thank you. D... what is the First Law of Thermodynamics?
当-热能-转换成-其它-能, 或者-反过来, 能量-总和-保持-不变.
When heat is transformed into any other kind of energy or vice versa,
the total quantity of energy remains invariable.
也-就是-说, 消失的-热能-和-新产生的-其它-类型的-能-在量上-是-相同的...
That is to say, the quantity of heat which disappears
is equivalent to the quantity of other kind of energy produced...
笨蛋! 你以为你在干什么?
Fool! What do you think you're doing?
我在救你的命!
I'm saving your life!
出去! 出去!
Get out! Get out!
啊!... 啊!... 啊!... 我-扛住-了, 啊, 没有-受损.
Ah!... Ah!... Ah!... Ah!... I have, ah, sustained no damage.
It's all right to _?FIXME
你甩开他们了?
You were able to get away then?
是的. Lesterson 和监察员在一起. Hensell 呢?
Yes. Lesterson's with the Examiner. And Hensell?
在和产品经理们开会. 现在我说了算.
At a meeting of production managers. He left me in control.
现在我们可以接管这个基地了.
We could take over the colony now.
不. 必须做到万无一失. 我可不想接管一个满是叛乱分子的基地, Janley?
No. No it has to be absolutely right.
I don't want to take over a colony full of rebels do I, Janley?
我也不清楚. 是你让我帮助他们.
Well, I don't know. You're making me help them.
把他们搅乱, 多制造些问题, 就可以把 Hensell 搞下去了. 然后我们再镇压他们.
Only to stir them up to create enough trouble to get rid of Hensell,
and then... and then we crush them.
这样我们就是基地的功臣, 我就是总督了.
The whole colony will be grateful, and I'll be Governor.
这就是你跟我说过的那种枪?
Is that the gun you told me of?
你能说服那些叛乱分子, 说这对他们很有用吗?
Can you persuade the rebels this will help them?
是的, Valmar 认为他可以做一个开关.
Yes, Valmar thinks he can work in a switch to turn it on and off.
这有多厉害?
How powerful is it?
它杀死了 Resno, Lesterson 的助手. Lesterson 还以为 Resno 只是晕倒了, 需要休息几天而已.
It killed Resno, Lesterson's assistant, and Lesterson believes
that Resno's simply shaken up - taking a few days off.
尸体呢?
And the body?
扔进水银沼泽了. 其实是 Lesterson 害死了他.
In the mercury swamp. Lesterson was the indirect cause of Resno's death.
这是个不错的把柄, 不怕他不听话了. 那我把这个交给 Valmar 去了?
It's a good hold over him if he makes trouble.
I'll give this to Valmar then?
好.
Yes.
我们什么时候行动?
When do we move?
我手里还缺一张牌. 那个监察员让我不放心.
I need another card in my hand. The Examiner bothers me.
我以为 Quinn 才是危险.
I thought Quinn was the danger.
哦, 不再是了. 那个监察员不是傻子. 不对, 这里还得搞点事儿.
Uh, not any more. The Examiner is no fool.
No, there has to be something else.
哦?
Well?
他不在实验室里, 只有 Lesterson 一个人.
Well, he's not in the laboratory, Lesterson's by himself.
嗯. 他肯定从别的路走了. 把你一个人留在这里行吗? 我打算回休息室去.
Hmm. He must have gone another way. Can I leave it you?
I'm going to go back to the rest room.
不过...
Well, but...
总有人得把它打扫一下吧.
Well, somebody's got to clear it up.
好吧.
Okay.
哈罗.
Hello there.
哈喽. 唔, 你是 Lesterson 的助手吧?
Hello. Um, you're Lesterson's assistant aren't you?
是的. 你不是在找监察员吧?
Yes. You're not looking for the Examiner are you?
那, 你知道他在哪儿吗?
Well, do you know where he is?
他在等一条地球来的消息, 他在通讯室.
Yes, he's waiting to get a message through from Earth.
He's in the Communications Room.
唔...
Umm...
哦, 你会发现很简单的.  拐过去, 在你的右手边, 下一个区就是.
Oh, you'll find it easy enough. Look.
Around, then to your right, in the next block.
太感谢了.
Thanks very much.
博士? 这里有人吗?
Doctor? Anyone here?
干得好 Valmar. 按住. 按住.
Well done Valmar. Hold her. Hold her.
好了, 这能让她安静一会儿了.
There, that'll keep her quiet for a bit.
我不知道她是谁. 她在这里探头探脑的.
I've no idea who she is. She was just snooping around.
我让她过来的. 我们期望她别碍我们的事. 叫一两个你的人把她弄到一个安全的地方.
I sent her. We want her kept out of the way.
Get a couple of your men to keep her in a safe place.
这是我跟你说过的东西.
Now, this is what I told you about.
是的. 致命能量应该是从这里出来的.
Yes. The lethal power must come from here.
哦.
Uh, huh.
它的射程应该也很不错.
It should have quite a good range.
你能修好它吗?
Can you fix it?
很简单. 这东西可以帮我们赢得这场革命.
It's easy. This could win us the revolution.
啊...
Ahh...
她说了她回这里来的. 她认识路, 也不会乱转, 我知道她不会的. 噢!
She said she was coming back here. She knew the way,
and she wouldn't have wandered off. I know she wouldn't! Oh!
Ben, 如果你是一个 Dalek 你下一步要做什么?
Ben, if you were a Dalek what would be your next move?
我说的是 Polly.
I'm talking about Polly.
哦, 不不不. 她是个聪明的女孩儿, 但她回答不了这个.
Oh, no, no, no, no. She's a clever girl, but she couldn't answer this.
她失踪了!
But she is missing!
哦, 不不不.
Oh, no, no, no.
哦, 是是是是!
Oh, yes, yes, yes, yes!
不不不! 她四处逛逛而已, 这里有好多东西可以看. 她对这些很感兴趣. 我喜欢这一点.
No, no, no! She's looking around, there's a lot to see in the colony.
She's interested. I like that.
来吧.
Come on.
我们要去哪儿?
Where are we going?
去报告. 如果我们要傻等, 我可不想! 我们去报告!
To report it. If we make a fool of ourselves,
I don't care! We report it!
还好. 我总算及时阻止了那个傻蛋监察员.
Yes, yes, yes. I managed to stop that fool of an Examiner just in time.
You know there are some people here who believe that you're an enemy.
你知道这里的一些人会认为你是我们的敌人.
我-是-你的-仆人.
I am your servant.
这台-机器-是做-什么-的?
What does this machine do?
你看, 很神奇的. 你有着人类一样的兴趣和好奇心.
You know, it's amazing.
You have an almost human interest and curiosity.
Dalek-比人类...跟人类-不太-一样. 如果-要我-帮忙, 我得-知道-所有-事情.
A Dalek is bet... is not the same as a human.
If I am to help, I must know everything.
是的, 当然.
Yes. Yes, of course.
这个-是-什么-机器?
What is this machine?
它是用来计算陨石风暴的, 以免它们损坏我们的气象卫星.
It computes meteorite storms as they approach our weather satellites.
它有-多-准确?
How accurate is it?
大约70％. 它对于降低卫星损失很有帮助.
About, ah, seventy percent.
It helps to cut down on our satellite losses.
Daleks-可以-建造-计算机-准确度-达到-百分之百.
Daleks can build pu... computers with one hundred percent accuracy.
百分之百?
One hundred percent?
如果-你能-提供-材料, 并给-我们-提供-能量, 计算机-将会-造好.
If you provide materials and our own power unit, a computer will be built.
百分之百. 那对于这个基地将是巨大的节约!
A hundred percent. That would be an enormous saving for the... for the colony!
那么-你能-拿到-材料-吗?
Then, you will get the materials?
我马上去跟总督说.
I'll go and speak to the Governor at once.
当你-回来-的时候-我-将把-蓝图-准备好.
I will be ready to dictate the blueprint when you return.
嚯. 那真是太棒了!
Huh, huh. Oh, that's marvellous!
你同意我们去找 Bragen 的.
You agreed we'd go and see Bragen.
唔? 能量.
Hmm? Power.
快点啊!
Come on then!
Daleks 的能量入口应该是那个方块...
Now the energy intake for Daleks should be the cube...
既然...
Now then...
你到底在做什么?
Well, now what are you at?
自言自语.
Talk to yourself.
哦, 数据不完整的话就没有用了!
Oh, it's useless with incomplete data!
Lesterson!
嗯?
Eh?
他刚走过去了. 也就是说我们又可以进他的实验室了.
He just went past. That means we can get into his laboratory again.
但我们要去找...
But we're looking for...
哦, 来吧, Ben. 过来.
Oh, come along, Ben. Come along.
这里有人.
There's somebody in there.
你在-这里-干什么?
What are you doing here?
站一边去. 仆人不应该管这个.
Stand aside. Servants shouldn't question.
入口-被-禁了.
Entry is restricted.
对我没有. "授予一切权限". 我有这个徽章.
Not for me it isn't. "Accord every access". I've got a badge.
这是-命令.
That is an order.
Dalek 的命令. 去把生成器弄短路了, Ben.
A Dalek order. Short circuit the generator, Ben.
啊!... 啊!!... 靠后站!
Ah!... Ah!... Ah!... Ah!... Ah!... Stand back!
别怕它 Ben. 它没有武器了. 我倒要看看他打算在这里做什么.
Don't be frightened of it Ben. It's not armed.
I'm going to see what it was doing in there.
Ben, 我们快出去!
Ben, let's get out of here!
蠢啊. Lesterson 一定重新激活他们了.
Fool. Lesterson must have reactivated them.
是的. 当我说跑的时候, 像个兔子一样快跑. 跑!
Yes. When I say run, run like a rabbit. Run!
我-已经-让人类-去-准备-材料了.
I have sent the human being for materials.
还有-能量?
And power?
是. 我们-能把-能量-转换为-静电, 然后-我们-就可-征服.
Yes. Power we can turn into static, then we will conquer.
我们-将要-征服... 我们-将要-征服... 我们-将要-征服...
We will conquer... We will conquer... We will conquer...
但是如果不是你干的 Lesterson, 那么 Dalek 肯定是自己用你提供的电源激活了其它几个
But if you didn't do it Lesterson, then the Dalek must
have used your power supply and reactivated the others itself.
我正要去激活它们呢.
I was going to do that anyway.
你脑子秀逗了, 伙计? 他们是带武器的!
Are you off your head, mate? Those two are armed!
那我们关掉电力供应, 解除他们的武装, 不就万事大吉了.
Then we turn off the electricity, disarm them,
and then everything is safe again.
我已经跟你解释过了.
I've already explained to you.
停止这些争论吧, 你俩都别说了, 我受够了.
Stop these arguments, both of you. I've had enough.
我对 Lesterson 有绝对信心. 从现在开始他将获得全权委托.
I've every confidence in Lesterson.
He has carte blanche for the Daleks from now on.
但他们必须被销毁掉!
But they must be destroyed!
Bragen, 我要下去巡视了, 在此期间这里你说了算
Bragen, I'm making a tour of the perimeter.
I put you in direct charge here.
确保 Lesterson 这里想要什么就给他什么, 好吧?
See that Lesterson gets everything he wants, will you?
我实验室还需要一个保安, Bragen.
I shall need a permanent guard on my laboratory, Bragen.
别担心监察员. 我想我能让他保持安静.
Don't worry about the Examiner. I think I can keep him quiet.
我们全都忘了 Polly.
We've been forgetting about Polly.
贪婪, 野心勃勃, 那就是它们的本性. 等着吧, 看看他们美妙的产品图能带给他们什么代价!
Greed and ambition, that's all it is. Wait till they find out
what their precious production figures have cost them!
哦, 我正要去找你呢.
Oh, I want to see you.
为了什么?
What about?
是 Polly, 她失踪. 我们在哪儿都找不到她.
Well it's Polly, she's missing. We can't find her anywhere.
我安排一个人去找找, 应该很快就可以找到她.
I'll tell one of my men to make enquiries.
It shouldn't take long to find her.
多谢了.
Ah, thanks.
监察员, 我的几个手下在水银沼泽里发现了一具尸体, 是一个中年人的.
Examiner, some of my men have found a body in the mercury swamp.
It was the body of a middle-aged man.
这跟我有什么关系吗?
What is that to do with me?
你是监察员啊 - 除非你不是.
You're the Examiner - or maybe you're not.
你这么说是什么意思?
Just exactly what do you mean by that?
你是谁? Quinn 的朋友? 是来制造骚乱?
Who are you? Quinn's friends? Come to stir up rebellion?
如果你认为我不是监察员, 那只有一种可能.
There's only one possible way that you could know I'm not the Examiner.
是的, 那就是知道真正的监察员长什么样!
Yeah, by knowing what the real Examiner looked like!
很对, Ben. 很对! 只有两个人知道他抵达这个星球时的情形：我和杀他的人.
Exactly, Ben. Exactly! Only two people knew of his arrival
on this planet. Myself and his murderer.
够了!
That's enough!
是这样? 博士, 我们去告诉总督.
Is it? Doctor, we've got to tell the Governor.
你觉得他会相信你? 我很快就可以让他相信是你杀了那个人, 还偷了那个人的徽章.
Do you think he'll believe you? I'll soon convince him
that you murdered the man yourself. You stole the Examiner's badge.
那你为什么不逮捕我们? 因为这里还有疑问, 对不? 因为有可能不往你想的方向发展.
Then why don't you arrest us? Because there's a doubt isn't there?
Because it might, it just might, go against you.
好吧, 好吧, 我们谁也不想先动. 但你们离 Lesterson 远点 - 还有 Daleks!
All right, all right, so neither of us wants to make a move.
But you leave Lesterson alone - and the Daleks!
他要做一个圣诞老人, 对不
He'd make a right Father Christmas, wouldn't he?
哦, 我宁可跟一百个他这种人斗, 也不想碰到一个 Dalek.
Oh, I'd rather fight a hundred of his sort than just one Dalek.
听听. "女孩儿很安全. 只要你们远离 Daleks, 她就是安全的".
Listen to this. "The girl is safe.
She will remain so as long as you leave the Daleks alone".
你解除了另外两个的武器?
And did you disarm the other two?
是的-我们-是-你的-仆人-我们-不-需要-武器.
Yes. We are your servants. We do not need guns.
我很高兴. 我知道监察员看错你们了.
I'm very glad. I knew the Examiner was wrong about you.
你-给-我们-带来-材料-了-吗?
Did you get our materials?
是的. 你们想要什么都行.
Yes. Everything you need you can have.
还有-一个-电厂?
And a power plant?
都行.
Everything.
我们-将要-获得-能量(权力)!
We will get our power.